Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Records WAG.022
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Subject Files
  - Subseries VII:B: President's Office Subject Files
    - Nurses (School): Clippings, 1971-1994 (Box 254, Folder 12)
    - Nurses (School): United Federation of Teachers chapter, 1978-1982 (Box 254, Folder 13)
    - Obituaries, 1969-1990 (Box 254, Folder 14)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville: Clippings, Jan 1968-Aug 1968 (Box 254, Folder 15)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville: Clippings, Sep 1968 (Box 254, Folder 16)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville: Clippings, Nov 1, 1968-Nov 19, 1968 (Box 254, Folder 17)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville: Clippings, Nov 16, 1968-Nov 30, 1968 (Box 254, Folder 18)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville: Clippings, Dec 1968 (Box 254, Folder 19)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville: Clippings, 1969 (Box 254, Folder 20)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville: Clippings, 1970-1978 (Box 254, Folder 21)
    - Open Classroom, 1965-1967 (Box 254, Folder 22)
    - Open Classroom, 1971-1975, undated (Box 254, Folder 23)
    - Operation Solomon: The Return of the Ethiopian Jews to Israel, 1992 (Box 254, Folder 24)
    - Paraprofessionals, 1969-1980 (Box 254, Folder 25)
    - Paraprofessionals: Articles, 1966-1979 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Paraprofessionals: Clippings, 1967-1986 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Paraprofessionals: City University of New York, courses, 1971 (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Paraprofessionals: Parascope, 1974-1980 (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - Parents: Articles, 1968-1994 (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - Parents: Parents Groups, 1950-1994 (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Parents: Roles, Rights, 1967-1994 (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - Parents: School Choice, 1993-1994 (Box 255, Folder 8)
    - Parks and Playgrounds, 1974-1991 (Box 255, Folder 9)
    - Parochial Schools: Address from Convention, 1960 (Box 255, Folder 10)
    - Pensions: Articles, pamphlets, 1965-1989 (Box 255, Folder 11)
    - Pensions: Attacks on, 1972-1991 (Box 255, Folder 12)
    - Pensions: Benefits Claim Examination, transcript, undated (Box 255, Folder 13)
    - Pensions: Clippings, 1976-1994 (Box 255, Folder 14)
    - Pensions: Cost of Living Adjustment, 1966-1990 (Box 255, Folder 15)
    - Pensions: Early Retirement, 1984-1990 (Box 255, Folder 16)
    - Pensions: Investments, 1976-1990 (Box 255, Folder 17)
    - Pensions: Mayor's Management Advisory Board, 1975-1976 (Box 255, Folder 18)
    - Pensions: New York City, 1973-1980 (Box 255, Folder 19)
    - Pensions: Pension Plan, 1975 (Box 255, Folder 20)
    - Pensions: Report, "Pension Changes in New York City, 1962-1972" (Box 255, Folder 21)
    - Pensions: Task Force, Statement, 1980 (Box 255, Folder 22)
    - Pensions: Tier 1, 1972-1989 (Box 255, Folder 23)
    - Pensions: Tier 2, 1973-1980 (Box 255, Folder 24)
    - Pensions: Tiers 3 and 4, 1976-1989 (Box 255, Folder 25)
    - Performance Contracting, 1970 (Box 255, Folder 26)
    - Performance Contracting, 1971-1972 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Performance Contracting: Clippings, 1970-1972 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - Performance Contracting: Texarkana Project, 1970 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Performing Arts, 1970-1988 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Performing Arts: Enriched Curriculum, 1982-1988 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Policies, 1975-1993 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Philippines: Teachers, 1980 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Physical Disabilities, 1976-1993 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Pledge of Allegiance and Loyalty Oaths, 1963-1988 (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Police Department: Bargaining, 1964-1994 (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - Police Department: Civilian Review Board, 1966 (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Police Department: Clippings, 1964-1990 (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - Politics: Democratic Left, the, 1973-1974 (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - Politics: Democratic Party, 1972-1988 (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - Politics: Far left, 1976-1980 (Box 256, Folder 15)
    - Politics: Far Right, 1985-1994 (Box 256, Folder 16)
    - Politics: General (PAC's, Voter Registration, etc), 1974-1989 (Box 256, Folder 17)
    - Politics: Larouche, Lyndon, undated (Box 256, Folder 18)
    - Politics: Republican Party, 1974-1989 (Box 256, Folder 19)
    - Politics: Social Democrats and Socialists, 1971-1978 (Box 256, Folder 20)
    - Political Action: Frontlash, 1972, undated (Box 256, Folder 21)
    - Political Action: Voter Registration, 1972 (Box 256, Folder 22)
    - Post-High School, 1970-1981 (Box 256, Folder 23)
    - Privatizing Schools, 1988-1994 (Box 256, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings: General, 1965-1982 (Box 256, Folder 25)
    - Prisons: New York State, 1976-1978, 1981 (Box 256, Folder 26)
    - Prisons: Instruction and Rehabilitation in, 1957-1958, 1969-1991 (Box 256, Folder 27)
    - Problems: Redistricting, etc, 1994 (Box 256, Folder 28)
    - Professional and White Collar Unions, 1965-1988 (Box 256, Folder 29)
    - Promotion, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 30)
    - Promotion Policy, 1966-1980, undated (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Promotion Policy: Promotions, Diplomas, 1981-1995 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Promotion Policy: Report Cards, Tracking, ca.1938, 1970-1987 (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Psychologists and Social Workers in Schools, 1965-1991 (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Publications: Brochures, Miscellaneous (Non-UFT), undated (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Publications: Brochures, Miscellaneous (UFT), undated (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Publications: Information for New Teachers, undated (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Publications: New York Urban Coalition, 1967 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Public Education Association, 1970-1976 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Public Employees, 1976-1988 (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - Public Employees: Clippings, 1968-1981 (Box 257, Folder 11)
    - Public Employees: General, 1976-1981 (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - Public Opinion regarding Schools, Teachers, etc., 1955-1990 (Box 257, Folder 13)
    - Puerto Rico, 1969-1980, undated (Box 257, Folder 14)
    - Race Relations: Poetry Contest, 1987 (Box 257, Folder 15)
    - Rapp-Coudert Committee, 1941 (Box 257, Folder 16)
    - Retired Teachers Chapter, 1964-1967, 1976, undated (Box 257, Folder 17)
    - Retired Teachers Chapter, 1992-1993 (Box 257, Folder 18)
    - Salary Schedule, 1982 (Box 257, Folder 19)
    - Sanitation Department: Union, DeLury, etc, 1975-1991 (Box 257, Folder 20)
    - Scholarship Fund: Agreement, 1971-1973 (Box 257, Folder 21)
    - Scholarship Fund: Annual Reports, 1971-1983 (Box 257, Folder 22)
    - Scholarship Fund: Application Sample, 1981-1984 (Box 257, Folder 23)
    - Scholarship Fund: Awardees, Status, 1973-1983 (Box 257, Folder 24)
    - Scholarship Fund: Award Presentation, 1976 (Box 257, Folder 25)
    - Scholarship Fund: Award Winners, 1976-1981 (Box 257, Folder 26)
    - Scholarship Fund: Board of Trustees, minutes, 1971-1982 (Box 257, Folder 27)
    - Scholarship Fund: Correspondence, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1975-1984 (Box 257, Folder 28)
    - Scholarship Fund: Forms and Form Letters, 1976, undated (Box 257, Folder 29)
    - Scholarship Fund: Miscellaneous, 1972-1976, undated (Box 257, Folder 30)
    - School Finance, 1972, 1975, undated (Box 257, Folder 31)
    - School Finance: Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 257, Folder 32)
    - School Finance: Budget, 1967, 1968-1969 (Box 257, Folder 33)
    - School Finance: Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 257, Folder 34)
    - School Finance: City and State, Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 257, Folder 35)
    - School Finance: Funded Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 257, Folder 36)
    - School Finance: Funded Programs, 1971-1973 (Box 257, Folder 37)
    - School Finance: New York City Fiscal Crisis, 1975 (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - School Finance: New York State Task Force, 1974-1976 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - School Finance: New York State Task Force, Reports, 1975 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - School Finance: New York State Task Force, Reports, 1982 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - School Finance: Papers and Brochures, 1969-1979, undated (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - School Finance: State Aid, 1978-1979 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - School Finance: State Aid, 1980-1981 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - School Finance: State Aid, 1982 (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - School Finance: State Aid, Report, undated (Box 258, Folder 9)
    - School Stability Team (NYC): Report and "Anatomy of a Crisis", 1972 (Box 258, Folder 10)
    - Schools: Health Hazards (Asbestos), 1972-1994 (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Schools: Health Hazards (Lead, etc), 1965-1994 (Box 258, Folder 12)
    - Selden, David, 1945-1974 (Box 258, Folder 13)
    - Shanker, Albert: Articles about, 1969-1998 (Box 258, Folder 14)
    - Shanker, Albert: Articles by, 1965-1990 (Box 258, Folder 15)
    - Shanker, Albert: Awards, 1990 (Box 258, Folder 16)
    - Shanker, Albert: Biographical, 1959-1995 (Box 258, Folder 17)
    - Shanker, Albert: Clippings, 1969 (Box 258, Folder 18)
    - Shanker, Albert: Debate with John Doar, Board of Education President, 1968 (Box 258, Folder 19)
    - Shanker, Albert: General, 1965-1985 (Box 258, Folder 20)
    - Shanker, Albert: "How We Knew Him": A Memorial Tribute, 1997 (Box 258, Folder 21)
    - Shanker, Albert: Interviews with, 1968-1974 (Box 258, Folder 22)
    - Shanker, Albert: Jailing, 1967 (Box 258, Folder 23)
    - Shanker, Albert: Memorials, 1997 (Box 258, Folder 24)
    - Shanker, Albert: Obituaries, 1997 (Box 258, Folder 25)
    - Shanker, Albert: Oral Histories, 1985-1988 (Box 258, Folder 26)
    - Shanker, Albert: "Solidarity Forever", 1997 (Box 258, Folder 27)
    - Shanker, Albert: Speeches, 1976 (Box 258, Folder 28)
    - Shanker, Albert: Urban Review interview, 1968 (Box 258, Folder 29)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1970 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1971 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1972 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1973 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1974 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1975 (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1976 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1977 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1978 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1979 (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1980 (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1981 (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1982 (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1983 (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1984 (Box 259, Folder 15)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1985 (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1986 (Box 259, Folder 17)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1987 (Box 259, Folder 18)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1988 (Box 259, Folder 19)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1989 (Box 259, Folder 20)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1990 (Box 259, Folder 21)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1991 (Box 259, Folder 22)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1992 (Box 259, Folder 23)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1993 (Box 259, Folder 24)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1994 (Box 259, Folder 25)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1995 (Box 259, Folder 26)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints, 1996 (Box 259, Folder 27)
    - Shanker, Albert: New York Times Column Reprints: UFT Booklets, 1973 (Box 259, Folder 28)
    - Special Districts: Intermediate School 201, 1966-1967 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Special Districts: Intermediate School 201, 1968 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Special Districts: Intermediate School 201, 1969 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Special Districts: Intermediate School 201, 1970 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Special Districts: Intermediate School 201, Ocean Hill-Brownsville, and Two Bridges, 1969-1970 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Special Districts: Intermediate School 227, 1979-1984 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Special Districts: Two Bridges, 1967-1970 (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils, 1973-1975 (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils, 1976-1994 (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Blind Students, 1975-1994 (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Board of Education, 1976-1979 (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Brain Damaged, 1970-1991 (Box 260, Folder 12)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Clippings, 1970-1994 (Box 260, Folder 13)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Deaf and Speech Impaired Students, 1969-1994 (Box 260, Folder 14)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Dyslexia, 1980-1990 (Box 260, Folder 15)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Emotional and Social Problems, 1976-1990 (Box 260, Folder 16)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Finance, 1976-1994 (Box 260, Folder 17)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Homebound or in Hospital, 1976-1990 (Box 260, Folder 18)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Laws and Regulations, 1972-1975 (Box 260, Folder 19)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Legal Cases, 1976-1990 (Box 260, Folder 20)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Mainstreaming, 1975 (Box 260, Folder 21)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Mainstreaming, 1976-1994 (Box 260, Folder 22)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: New York State, 1974-1978 (Box 260, Folder 23)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Personnel, 1976-1993 (Box 260, Folder 24)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Private Schools, 1977-1988 (Box 260, Folder 25)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: Transportation, 1975-1988 (Box 260, Folder 26)
    - Special Education, Special Needs Pupils: UFT and NYSUT, 1974-1980 (Box 260, Folder 27)
    - State Support of Schools, 1978-1990 (Box 260, Folder 28)
    - Statistics, 1976-1993 (Box 260, Folder 29)
    - Teachers, 1975-1986 (Box 260, Folder 30)
    - Strike: Clippings, Sep 4, 1968-Sep 10, 1968 (Box 260, Folder 31)
    - Strike: Clippings, Sep 11, 1968-Sep 20, 1968 (Box 260, Folder 32)
    - Strike: Clippings, Sep 21, 1968-Sep 30, 1968 (Box 260, Folder 33)
    - Strike: Clippings, Oct 1, 1968-Oct 16, 1968 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Strike: Clippings, Oct 17, 1968-Oct 31, 1968 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Strike: Teachers, 1969 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Susquehanna Valley Teachers Association, 1974-1976 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Teachers Assigned, 1975-1976 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Teachers Employees Association (TEA), 1967, undated (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - Teachers Union, 1938 (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Testing: Educational Testing Service and Regents, 1961-1994 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Testing: IQ, 1964-1991 (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Testing: Magazine Articles, Disquisitions, Handbooks, 1973-1977 (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Testing: Press, 1972-1994 (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Truants, 1985, 1993-1994 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - Tuition Tax Credit, 1965-1990 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - United Federation of Teachers: Awards, 1960, 1970-1991 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - United Federation of Teachers: History, 1963-1985 (Box 261, Folder 15)
    - Urban Review(magazine), 1968-1969 (Box 261, Folder 16)
    - United States Department of Education, 1969-1988 (Box 261, Folder 17)
    - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (HEW): Teachers National Task Force, 1974-1984 (Box 261, Folder 18)
    - United Teachers of New York and New York State Teachers Association, undated (Box 261, Folder 19)
    - United Teachers of New York and New York State Teachers Association: Clippings, 1971 (Box 261, Folder 20)
    - United Teachers of New York and New York State Teachers Association: Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 261, Folder 21)
    - Vouchers, 1970-1973 (Box 261, Folder 22)
    - Wages: General, 1954-1990 (Box 261, Folder 23)
    - Wilson, Malcolm, 1973-1974 (Box 261, Folder 24)
    - Woodbridge, NJ Teachers Jailed, 1967-1977 (Box 261, Folder 25)
    - Workers Rights, 1973, undated (Box 261, Folder 26)
    - Working Conditions, 1973-1993 (Box 261, Folder 27)
- Series VIII: Sandra Feldman Files, 1965-1997
  - Subseries VIII:A: Member Correspondence, 1984-1997
    - Correspondence: Member, Anonymous, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Member, A, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Member, Bach-Bernstein, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Member, Biebert-Byrd, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Member, C, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Member, D, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Member, E, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Member, F, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Member, Gabel-Goldman, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Member, Goldstein-Gwillym, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Member, Haber-Hentrich, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Member, Herman-Hyman, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Member, I, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Member, J, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Member, Kamchi-Kelly, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Member, Kerner-Kwit, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Member, Landau-Lieberman, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Member, Liebov-Lyon, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Member, Mack-Mayglothling, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Member, McCarthy-Michaels, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Member, Milan-Murtha, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Member, N, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Member, O, 1986 (Box 262, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Member, P, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Member, Raines-Roberts, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Member, Robinson-Russo, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Member, Sabath-Scott, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Member, Seacrest-Singer, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Member, Singh-Szott, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Member, T, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Member, U-V, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Member, Wagner-Wersching, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Member, Wertheim-Woytowich, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Member, X-Z, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Member, Anonymous, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Member, A, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Member, Babbush-Bergtram, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Member, Berkowitz-Bolnick, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Member, Bona-Burd, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Member, Caechi-Cleveland, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Member, Cohen-Curet, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Member, D, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Member, E, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Member, Fagella-Fitzpatrick, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Member, Fleischmann-Furst, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Member, Gabel-Goldberg, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Member, Goldman-Grossmen, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Member, Haber-Hitz, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Member, Hochler-Howort, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Member, I, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Member, J, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Member, Kachalsky-Kelly, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Member, Kelsick-Klimas, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Member, Knajdl-Kupferberg, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Member, Lanin-Levinson, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Member, Levitt-Lynes, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Member, Mack-McGuiness, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Member, McKeever-Mitton, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Member, Mizrahi-Myers, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Member, N, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Member, O, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Member, Packer-Porzio, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Member, Posman-Pucie, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Member, Q, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Member, Rackoff-Rodriguez, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Member, Rogovon-Ryan, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Member, Sabath-Schenker, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Member, Schiebel-Shands, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Member, Shapiro-Siodmack, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Member, Skeen-St.Cyr, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Member, Stein-Szott, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Member, T, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Member, U-V, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Member, Wagenhals-Weintraub, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Member, Weisen-Woodson, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Member, Y-Z, 1987 (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Member, Anonymous, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Member, Aarons-Angrilli, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Member, Anthony-Azarowicz, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Member, Babel-Beck, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Member, Becker-Bicjan, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Member, Bieger-Budin, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Member, Cahill-Caruso, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Member, Casaccio-Cohen, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Member, Cohl-Cuocolo, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Member, D, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Member, E, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Member, F, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Member, Gabel-Glaubman, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Member, Gloster-Green, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Member, Greenberg-Guzy, 1988 (Box 265, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Member, Haber-Hirsch, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Member, Hirschfeld-Hyman, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Member, I-J, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Member, Kahn-Kerenyi, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Member, Kern-Kurke, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Member, Lage-Levine, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Member, Levison-Lystad, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Member, MacDonald-McGowan, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Member, McGuire-Miller, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Member, Milowe-Myers, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Member, N, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Member, O, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Member, Pace-Potash, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Member, Porthoy-P.S.246X, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Member, Rabinowitz-Rosner, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Member, Ross-Ryles, 1988 (Box 266, Folder 16)